{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Outdoor \u0026 Landscape Lighting Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/39802/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39802,"taskName":"Outdoor Lighting - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Landscape Lighting or Outdoor Lighting","xmTaskDescriptor":"Outdoor \u0026 Landscape Lighting Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":154,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Outdoor Lighting backyard landscape lamps","textMessagingName":"Repr Outdoor Light","rolloverLongDesc":"Specialists who have detailed knowledge of fixtures \u0026 wiring techniques. Know how to use exterior lighting to enhance safety, security \u0026 the beauty of a property.","rolloverShortDesc":"Exterior lighting for buildings \u0026 grounds.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Landscape Lighting or Outdoor Lighting.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Outdoor \u0026 Landscape Lighting Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Landscape Lighting Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Outdoor Light Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Lighting - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Outdoor Lighting Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Lighting-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Landscape Lighting Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Outdoor Lighting Companies","searchKeywords":"Outdoor,Lighting,backyard,landscape,lamps,yard,lawn","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":325,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39802/":{"taskOID":39802,"originalTaskOID":39802,"setID":325,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4023,"questionDisplayText":"Describe Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the  problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":727,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"All lights not working","answerDisplayText":"All lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5898,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Some lights not working","answerDisplayText":"Some lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3605,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lights need adjustment","answerDisplayText":"Lights need adjustment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1430,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Clock timer or photocell not working","answerDisplayText":"Clock timer or photocell not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3898,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Moisture intrusion","answerDisplayText":"Moisture intrusion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3583,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Light is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Light is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3604,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lights come on at wrong times","answerDisplayText":"Lights come on at wrong times","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4376,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Reposition lights\t","answerDisplayText":"One or more lights need to be repositioned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4022,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Repair Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of landscape lighting needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","answerDisplayText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":593,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent bullets (directional)","answerDisplayText":"Accent bullets (directional)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1074,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bollard lights","answerDisplayText":"Bollard lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6084,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Step lights","answerDisplayText":"Step lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4602,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Path lights","answerDisplayText":"Path lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway markers","answerDisplayText":"Driveway markers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6589,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Underwater well lights","answerDisplayText":"Underwater well lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11131,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4023,"questionDisplayText":"Describe Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the  problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":727,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"All lights not working","answerDisplayText":"All lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5898,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Some lights not working","answerDisplayText":"Some lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3605,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lights need adjustment","answerDisplayText":"Lights need adjustment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1430,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Clock timer or photocell not working","answerDisplayText":"Clock timer or photocell not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3898,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Moisture intrusion","answerDisplayText":"Moisture intrusion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3583,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Light is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Light is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3604,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lights come on at wrong times","answerDisplayText":"Lights come on at wrong times","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4376,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Reposition lights\t","answerDisplayText":"One or more lights need to be repositioned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":727,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"All lights not working","answerDisplayText":"All lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5898,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Some lights not working","answerDisplayText":"Some lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3605,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lights need adjustment","answerDisplayText":"Lights need adjustment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1430,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Clock timer or photocell not working","answerDisplayText":"Clock timer or photocell not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3898,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Moisture intrusion","answerDisplayText":"Moisture intrusion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3583,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Light is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Light is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3604,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lights come on at wrong times","answerDisplayText":"Lights come on at wrong times","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4376,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Reposition lights\t","answerDisplayText":"One or more lights need to be repositioned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4022,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Repair Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of landscape lighting needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","answerDisplayText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":593,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent bullets (directional)","answerDisplayText":"Accent bullets (directional)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1074,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bollard lights","answerDisplayText":"Bollard lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6084,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Step lights","answerDisplayText":"Step lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4602,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Path lights","answerDisplayText":"Path lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway markers","answerDisplayText":"Driveway markers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6589,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Underwater well lights","answerDisplayText":"Underwater well lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11131,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","answerDisplayText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":593,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent bullets (directional)","answerDisplayText":"Accent bullets (directional)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1074,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bollard lights","answerDisplayText":"Bollard lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6084,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Step lights","answerDisplayText":"Step lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4602,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Path lights","answerDisplayText":"Path lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway markers","answerDisplayText":"Driveway markers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6589,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Underwater well lights","answerDisplayText":"Underwater well lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11131,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}